0xBitcoin is the first fully decentralized ERC20 token
0xBitcoin是第一个完全去中心化的ERC20代币
and is the first purely mined token on Ethereum
并且是第一个完全在以太坊上开采的代币
and it aims to be the primary medium of exchange
该币的目标是成为一大主要的交易媒介
and store of value on the Ethereum network.
并在以太坊网络中存储价值。
The 0xBitcoin token was deployed to the Ethereum blockchain in
0xBitcoin代币已于2018年2月部署到以太坊区块链中
February 2018 with the following attributes:
它具有以下属性：
first mineable token,
第一个可挖掘的代币，
ERC20 compatible,
兼容ERC20标准，
no pre-mine or instamine,
不可预先或瞬时挖矿，
and no ICO.
不开展首次代币发行 (ICO)。
Ether was never intended to act as a currency, and
以太币从未计划成为货币，
0xBitcoin will allow Ether to fulfill its sole intended purpose
0xBitcoin将确保以太币实现其唯一的预期目的
of securing the Ethereum network.
即保障以太坊网络。
0xBitcoin takes the best properties of Bitcoin and Ethereum
0xBitcoin利用了比特币和以太坊的最佳特性
and combines them into one token.
将它们组合生成一个新代币。
It can be mined exactly like Bitcoin
可以完全像比特币那样进行挖矿
but transferred 10 times faster and 100 times cheaper.
但转账速度快10倍，而价格便宜100倍。
0xBitcoin combines the Bitcoin properties of
0xBitcoin结合了比特币的众多特性：
block rewards, proof-of-work issuance,
区块奖励、工作量证明发行，
and a 21 million coin cap
和2100万个币封顶
with the Ethereum properties of
并且兼具以太坊的特性：
speed, DApps, and DEX trading.
快速、去中心化的应用程序和去中心化交易。
And unlike Ether, it interfaces with smart contracts
与以太币不同的是，它与智能合约相关联
for storing and transferring value.
用于存储和转移价值。
While Bitcoin can only be traded using centralized means,
比特币只能通过集中式方法进行交易，
0xBitcoin can be traded permissionlessly via
0xBitcoin交易却可以在非许可条件下进行，
smart contracts which cannot be affected or controlled
即通过不受中央实体影响或控制的
by central entities.
智能合约完成交易。
It is also immune to 51% attacks.
它也不受51%攻击的影响。
Add all this to the proven market demand for a
所有这些都证明了市场对更快版本比特币的需求，
faster version of Bitcoin, as we've seen in
正如我们在莱特币的成功中所看到的那样，
Litecoin's success, and it is plain that
很明显的是，
0xBitcoin fills a hole in the crypto market space.
0xBitcoin填补了加密货币市场中的空白。
People are excited about the project in no small part due to
人们对这个项目充满期待，很大程度上是因为
the decentralization of the token
0xBitcoin代币的去中心化
and the active and engaged community
以及活跃的参与型社区，
which has sprung up around the token.
使得0xBitcoin社区大量涌现。
The community has achieved several key milestones
自项目启动以来，
since the project's launch, including
0xBitcoin社区已经取得了几个关键性里程碑，
creating an EIP specifically for mineable tokens,
包括创建了专门用于可开挖掘代币的EIP，
creation of mining pools with multiple new mining clients,
创建了具有一组新矿工的矿池，
as well as ongoing development of Lava Wallet,
以及Lava钱包的持续开发，
Quarry, and off-chain transactions.
矿场和链下交易。
0xBitcoin is a unique project, backed by a passionate community
0xBitcoin是一个与众不同的项目，
dedicated to making it the primary transfer of value
由充满激情的社区提供支持，
for the Ethereum network.
致力于成为以太坊网络价值的主要转移工具。